http://www.everywoman.co.uk/terms-conditions

Terms and conditions
Welcome to the everywoman websiteThis page (together with the documents referred to on it) tells you the terms on which you may make use of our website www.everywoman.com (“our site”), whether as a guest or a registered user, an everywomanNetwork member or an everywomanClub member. Please read these terms of use carefully before you start to use the site.By using this website you are deemed to have read and agreed to these terms and conditions: Information about usOur site is operated by Everywoman Limited ("this Company/We"), a company registered in England & Wales, Company No. 3798319 registered office: Woodstock House, Charlton Road, Charlton, West Sussex, PO18 0HU. We are registered for VAT No. 740229065Privacy Statement (including Cookies)We are committed to protecting your privacy. Please refer to our Privacy Policy (which includes our Cookies Policy) for details on how we do this.No information from children under age 13If you are under age 13, please do not attempt to register on this website or provide any personal information about yourself to us. If we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from a child under age 13, please contact us. Disclaimer and Exclusions and LimitationsThe information on this web site is provided on an "as is" basis. To the fullest extent permitted by law, this Company:excludes all representations and warranties relating to this website and its contents or which is or may be provided by any affiliates or any other third party, including in relation to any inaccuracies or omissions in this website and/or the Company’s literature; andexclude all liability for damages arising out of or in connection with your use of this website. This includes, without limitation, direct loss, loss of business or profits (whether or not the loss of such profits was foreseeable, arose in the normal course of things or you have advised this Company of the possibility of such potential loss), damage caused to your computer, computer software, systems and programs and the data thereon or any other direct or indirect, consequential and incidental damages.This Company does not however exclude liability for death or personal injury caused by its negligence. The above exclusions and limitations apply only to the extent permitted by law. None of your statutory rights as a consumer are affected. Termination of Agreements and Refunds PolicyBoth the Client and ourselves have the right to terminate any Services Agreement for any reason, including the ending of services that are already underway. No refunds shall be offered, where a Service is deemed to have begun and is, for all intents and purposes, underway. Any monies that have been paid to us which constitute payment in respect of the provision of unused Services, shall be refunded.All delgate passes, awards bookings and sponsorship fees paid for everywoman events are non-refundable. Delegate passes and awards tickets may be transferred to an alternative guest if notice is given in writing to events@everywoman.com no less than 5 working days prior to the event.Any everywomanAmbassador wishing to resign must do so in writing to Membership Committee, everywoman, Woodstock House, Charlton Road, Charlton, West Sussex, PO18 0HU or via email to contact@everywoman.com. Any everywomanNetwork member wishing to cancel their account should email contact@everywoman.com.  No refunds will be made whether on resignation, expiry or other termination of membership. All memberships are based on a yearly contract, and any resignation mid-way throughout the contract period will not be funded.Our right to suspend or cancel your registration:We may suspend or cancel your registration immediately at our reasonable discretion or if you breach any of your obligations under these Terms and Conditions.You can cancel your registration at any time by informing us in writing at Everywoman Limited, Woodstock House, Charlton Road, Charlton, West Sussex, PO18 0HU. If you do so, you must stop using our site.The suspension or cancellation of your registration and your right to use our site shall not affect either party's statutory rights or liabilities. AvailabilityYou are solely responsible for evaluating the fitness for a particular purpose of any download, program and text available through this site. Redistribution or republication of any part of this site or its content is prohibited, including such by framing or other similar or any other means, without the express written consent of the Company. The Company does not warrant that the service from this site will be uninterrupted, timely or error free, although it is provided to the best ability. By using this service you thereby indemnify this Company, its employees, agents and affiliates against any loss or damage, in whatever manner, howsoever caused.Links to this websiteWe reserve the right to ask you to remove links to our website from sites which go against the values of everywoman, or may cause the everywoman brand to be compromised. If you do create a link to a page of this website you do so at your own risk and the exclusions and limitations set out above will apply to your use of this website by linking to it.Links from this websiteWe do not monitor or review the content of other party’s websites which are linked to from this website. Opinions expressed or material appearing on such websites are not necessarily shared or endorsed by us and should not be regarded as the publisher of such opinions or material. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices, or content, of these sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site & to read the privacy statements of these sites. You should evaluate the security and trustworthiness of any other site connected to this site or accessed through this site yourself, before disclosing any personal information to them. This Company will not accept any responsibility for any loss or damage in whatever manner, howsoever caused, resulting from your disclosure to third parties of personal information.Your contentYou own any copyright in the text that you post or resources you upload on our website. However, when you post text or upload resources, you expressly grant us a perpetual, unlimited free license to republish that text/resource on our site and to redistribute/make available and/or sell that text/resource in print or electronic form anywhere in the world as part of an edited compilation or otherwise.Disclaimer of warranties and liabilityWe provide our site in good faith but we can't and don't warrant the completeness, truth or accuracy of the information or other content or postings found on our site, or their usefulness for any particular purpose. You acknowledge and agree that you bear full responsibility for your own contributions to the website and that we shall not be liable for any action that you or others take or don't take based on your use of or reliance on information provided by us or other users of this website.We don't promise that your access to our site, or its content will be delivered uninterrupted, timely or error-free, or that the site will be free from viruses or other harmful properties. It is your responsibility to implement satisfactory safeguards and procedures to make sure any files you obtain through our site are free from such contaminations or other harmful properties.The effect of what is set out here is that you agree that under no circumstances will we be held liable for any direct, indirect, incidental or other type loss or injury resulting from your use, or downloading of any content on our site.Discussion and User Communication SystemsWe encourage debate and the sharing of information between our users.Your details: You must ensure that the details provided by you on registration or at any time are correct and complete. You must inform us immediately of any changes to the information that you provided when registering by updating your personal details in order that we can communicate with you effectively.Password and security: When you register to use our platforms you will be asked to create a password. In order to prevent fraud, you must keep this password confidential and must not disclose it or share it with anyone. If you know or suspect that someone else knows your password you should notify us by contacting Everywoman Limited, Woodstock House, Charlton Road, Charlton, West Sussex, PO18 0HU or calling 020 7981 2574 immediately.If we have reason to believe that there is likely to be a breach of security or misuse of our forum, we may require you to change your password or we may suspend your account.You may not use any of our communication systems for any illegal purpose and in particular you will not:post or transmit material that infringes the intellectual property rights or other rights of others or post or transmit any material that is unlawful, obscene, defamatory, threatening, harassing, abusive, hateful, or embarrassing to any other person as determined by us in our sole discretionpost or transmit advertisements for or solicitations of businessafter receiving a warning, continue to disrupt the normal flow of dialogue, or post or transmit comments that are not related to the topic being discussedpost or transmit chain letters or pyramid schemesimpersonate another persondisguise the IP address of the connection used to post any messagepost or transmit any files containing viruses or other harmful computer codeharvest or otherwise collect or use information about others, including e-mail addresses, without their explicit consentallow any other person or entity to use your identification for posting or viewing comments or for communicating with other userspost the same note more than once or “spam”; orengage in any other conduct that restricts or inhibits any other person from using or enjoying these areas of our site, or which, in our judgment, exposes us to any liability or detriment of any typeintentionally make false or misleading statements about investments, their price or their prospects. If you do, you may be committing a criminal offence.post either intentionally or otherwise, any material that could have the effect of manipulating the market value of any investment. This may be a criminal offence.give investment advice by way of business or make financial promotions.Please note that any posting of information on our platforms is the opinion of the person posting only and in no way reflects our opinions or attitudes. We operate an open forum and sometimes messages are posted that are misleading, deceptive, or incorrect. You should not rely on information being accurate or complete. If you do, you do so at your own risk.We don't commit to monitor the use of the chat forums or our communications systems; we rely on you to inform us if you spot any abuse or inappropriate behaviour, in which case we will review specific postings. If you feel you have been threatened, damaged or abused in our chat forums or via our communications systems that we operate or if you believe any infringement of your rights may have occurred through our site please contact us.We reserve the right (but we are not obliged) to do any or all of the following:record the communications in chat forums and communications systemsinvestigate a claim that any one or more communication does not conform to the terms of this clause and determine in our sole discretion to remove or request the removal of the communication(s)remove without notice communications which are abusive, illegal, or disruptive, or that otherwise fail to conform with these Termsterminate a user's access to post messages to any or all of these areasmonitor, edit, or disclose any communication in these areas.edit or remove any communication(s) posted on our website, regardless of whether such communication(s) breaches these Terms.If you disagree with a decision of a member (e.g. comment flagged as inappropriate), you should appeal via contact us.Any decision we make to remove or request the removal of any communication or to terminate or suspend the posting privileges of any member shall be final and binding. The termination or suspension of posting privileges shall apply to any and all user accounts that may have been used by that person, whether or not opened by that person.IndemnityYou agree to indemnify, defend and hold harmless us, our directors, officers, employees and licensors from and against any claim, liability, cost, damage or loss we may incur (including reasonable legal fees) as a result of any material that you post or transmit on our communication forums or via our communication systems, any actions you take which disrupt access to and/or the functioning of our site or any breach by you of your obligations under these Terms.Intellectual PropertyWe are the owner or the licensee of all intellectual property rights in our site, and in the material published on it.  Those works are protected by copyright laws and treaties around the world.  All such rights are reserved.You may print off one copy, and may download extracts, of any page(s) from our site for your personal reference and you may draw the attention of others within your organisation to material posted on our site. You must not modify the paper or digital copies of any materials you have printed off or downloaded in any way, and you must not use any illustrations, photographs, video or audio sequences or any graphics separately from any accompanying text.Our status (and that of any identified contributors) as the authors of material on our site must always be acknowledged.You must not use any part of the materials on our site for commercial purposes without obtaining a licence to do so from us or our licensors.If you print off, copy or download any part of our site in breach of these terms of use, your right to use our site will cease immediately and you must, at our option, return or destroy any copies of the materials you have made.The everywoman logo is a registered trademark of this Company in the United Kingdom and other countries.CommunicationWe have several different e-mail addresses for different queries. These, and other contact information, can be found on our Contact Us link on our website or via Company literature or via the Company’s stated telephone or facsimile.If you have joined the everywomanNetwork or everywomanClub you are automatically opted in to receive emails from everywoman and chosen third parties. You can opt out of these emails in your profile page, selecting 'Edit', followed by 'Profile' and unchecking the boxes in the 'Opt In' section.Force MajeureWe shall not be liable to you for any failure to perform any obligation under any Agreement which is due to an event beyond our control including but not limited to any Act of God, terrorism, war, Political insurgence, insurrection, riot, civil unrest, act of civil or military authority, uprising, earthquake, flood or any other natural or man made eventuality outside of our control, which causes the termination of an agreement or contract entered into, nor which could have been reasonably foreseen. If we are affected by such event, we shall forthwith inform you of the same and shall use all reasonable endeavours to comply with the terms and conditions of any Agreement contained herein.GeneralThe laws of England and Wales govern these Terms and Conditions and the English courts shall have non-exclusive jurisdiction in any claim arising from, or related to, a visit to our site including any non-contractual obligations.If any of these Terms and Conditions are deemed invalid or unenforceable for any reason (including, but not limited to the exclusions and limitations set out above), then the invalid or unenforceable provision will be severed from these Terms and Conditions and the remaining terms will continue to apply.Failure of the Company to enforce any of the provisions set out in these Terms and Conditions and any Agreement, or failure to exercise any option to terminate, shall not be construed as waiver of such provisions and shall not affect the validity of these Terms and Conditions or of any Agreement or any part thereof, or the right thereafter to enforce each and every provision.Notification of ChangesThe Company reserves the right to change these Terms and Conditions from time to time as it sees fit and your continued use of the site will signify your acceptance of any adjustment to these Terms and Conditions. If there are any changes to our Privacy Policy, we will announce that these changes have been made on our home page and on other key pages on our site. Any changes to our privacy policy will be posted on our web site 30 days prior to these changes taking place. You are therefore advised to re-read this statement on a regular basis.Last updated on: 14th July 2020.
